When you have a lot of people, they can
all be your hired amazing people.
They're very intelligent. But as the
scope of the task grows, it becomes a
lot more like managing organization. Do
we know to go and read to the right
document at the right time? Do we
remember our own selves from a year ago?
And so, a lot of these analogies apply
now to agents. And [music] some
organizational philosophy comes into how
do you make agents effective? From the
Tesla point of view, context is a big
part of the platform that we're
building. One of the terms that I know
every single day pretty much is agent
enablement. This is super important,
super powerful. What is agent enablement
and what's Tesla's role in that?
>> [music]
>> Yeah, I I feel uh we we should start
discussing in sort of outcome based
tools versus sort of the technical
elements. So, context is a
uh is a very important uh tool or sort
of means, context management of it. I
think the eventual goal that you want is
to enable the agents. Uh And uh I I find
sales enablement actually to be an
easier example uh even though in
development clearly like you think about
sort of onboarding. So, for developers,
you can think about you need to onboard
a developer. Uh so, you have a you know,
a brilliant developer come along, join
the team. You still don't expect them to
kind of know how to build well within
your organization the very first moment
they landed. You need them to be
onboarded. So, what are the materials
they need to read? And then over time,
there's some element of continuous
training. I think in development, it's a
little bit harder to to to uh
uh think about systemizing it cuz we
rely a lot of uh individual kind of uh
skills and individual talents. And you
know, for good or bad, we sort of rely
on this institutional knowledge. Uh
sales enablement is an interesting
analogy because uh often times as
organizations grow, you you want your
sales organization to be creative only
to a degree. You want them to repeat the
playbook. And so, sales is a much more
structured place in which you say,
"Okay, here are the enablement
materials. Hey, any new salesperson, you
need to read this. But also, every
existing salesperson, every year at
kickoff, we're going to teach you this
is this is the sales process. These are
the stages. These are the decks that you
need to do. These are the materials, the
emphasis, the messaging, you know, like
all the things that you need to provide.
And then, those get measured, you know,
and they get monitored. And we identify
the cases where some random behavior was
successful or when something falls
through. And then, you redefine a bunch
of those practices. And then, you train
them again, you know, to build those.
And so, agents are I I think that's
maybe a slightly closer technical
analogy to what we do with the agent
enablement. So, your eventual goal is to
say, "Hey, I want agents to work in my
organizations and specifically in my
development uh
and in my codebase. I want them to build
well for me." So, how do I how do I make
them successful? What is the knowledge I
need to equip them with? How do I uh
kind of evaluate, you know, role play
and test and sort of see that that
works, which is something we can't do as
as well with people. We can be a lot
more demanding with agents. You know,
how do I distribute that knowledge? How
do I then observe
behavior and sort of see when did it
actually happen. And then, how do you
take that and optimize it? And when we
apply it to agents, we see all these
super interesting things that we'll
continue to share
uh over the over the next
uh kind of couple of months uh is all
these like really interesting
observations, you know, like when when
we when we look at agent logs and what
do they create, you can see how some
instructions you put in your context,
uh they just ignore. They just don't do.
And you see how other instructions, they
will do it when we do the the AB test,
when we evaluate with and without those
instructions, they do the same thing
anyway. So, if you try to get it to use
uh Git, it would use Git anyway. But if
you try to get it to use uh GH, you
know, instead as the CLI, you you really
need to say it in a very specific way to
kind of counter the intuitive way. And
so, if you said Git, you wasted context.
If you said GH in the wrong way, you're
not going to get your result. So, a lot
of a lot of those and eventually you
like you have to think about how do I
solve it? I have observed a problem. And
that comes back to you modify the
context, that's your tool. So, we we
think a lot about if you are an
organization, you want agents to work
uh for you, you need to enable those
agents. And context and the management
of that context, the optimization of
that context is the means through which
you do it.